<resource>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_105</key>
    <original>拳を地面に突き立て、自身を囲むように
柱状の錬成物質を生成する。高所から行うことで
威力が上昇する。空中でも発動可能
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に錬成値の上昇
LV.６で錬成物質の生成回数増加（１→２）&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Slam your fist into the ground and
surround yourself with pillars of alchemical metal. When 
performed from high altitudes, the power of the attack rises.
Can be activated even while in the air.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases amount of stakes planted upon contact.
LV.6: Increases the times the pillars raise (1→2)&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_104</key>
    <original>掌を地面に添え、振り上げると同時に
地を這う錬成物質の波を放つ
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に錬成値の上昇
LV.６で錬成物質の本数増加（３→５）／
敵を転倒させる効果追加&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Place your palm on the ground and upon
raising it, create waves of alchemical substances that spike
up along the ground.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases amount of stakes planted upon contact. 
LV.6: Increases number of waves (3→5) and adds the ability 
to juggle enemies.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_108</key>
    <original>炎、氷、雷の主要３属性を纏った
錬成式を地面から生成し空中に配置する
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に錬成式の継続時間が延長
LV.６で聖・闇の２属性追加&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Create an elemental orb that bestows
one of the three main attributes of fire, ice, or lightning,
from the ground and place it in the air.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases duration of the skill.
LV.6: Unlocks the final two elements, Holy and Darkness.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_109</key>
    <original>乗った者を高所へ跳ね上げる効果を持つ
錬成式を地面に配置する
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に錬成式の継続時間が延長
LV.６で空中にも設置可能になり、
空中に配置された場合は横方向に跳躍可能&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Place an alchemical trampoline on the ground
that launches those who jump on it to high altitudes.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases duration of the skill.
LV.6: Allows placement in the air. When placed mid-air,
you can be launched horizontally.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_107</key>
    <original>風を纏った錬成物質を生成し配置する
後退後に風の錬成球を叩くと、風圧が発生する
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に錬成球の継続時間が延長
LV.６で叩いた時に発生する風圧範囲が拡張&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Create a ball of wind-wrapped alchemical substances.
Wind pressure is generated when striking the ball after placement.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases duration of the skill.
LV.6: Increases range of wind pressure generated when struck.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_106</key>
    <original>素早く敵との間合いを詰め、錬成杭を打ち込む
杭を叩くと錬成値が増加する
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に杭の継続時間が延長
LV.６で移動距離が延長／始動後に範囲攻撃追加
杭を叩いた時の錬成値が上昇&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Drive alchemical piles into enemies, and quickly draw
their aggression. If a pile is struck, the amount of stakes on it will increase.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases duration of the skill.
LV.6: Increases chase range of skill, and amount of alchemical
stakes gained upon striking the pile.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_110</key>
    <original>錬成物質で罠を生成する。この罠に敵が
近付くと自動的に棘が放出され、対象を貫く
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に錬成罠の起動回数増加
LV.６で棘の本数が増加（１→３）&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Generate a trap from an alchemical substance.
When enemies approach the trap, pillars spike out from it and 
penetrate them.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases number of trap activations.
LV.6: Increases the number of pillar spikes (1→3)&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_111</key>
    <original>自身の体を金で覆い、敵の攻撃を遮断する
さらに攻撃した敵に対し黄金化の異常値を与える
空中でも発動可能
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に黄金化の異常値上昇
LV.６でダウン、拘束中を除きいつでも発動可能&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Coat yourself in gold and deflect enemy attacks.
Enemies that attack will build up the "Gilded" status abnormality.
Can be activated even while in the air.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases rate of Gilding build-up.
LV.6: Can activate the skill at anytime except when grabbed.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_112</key>
    <original>敵を直接攻撃し、攻撃対象の敵単体に付着している
錬成物質を解放して大爆発を起こす
しがみつき状態からも発動可能
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に攻撃威力の上昇
LV.６でヒット数増加／爆発に周囲の敵を巻き込む&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Bring forth a giant metal arm that strikes the 
enemy directly and can adhere to them if it hits an alchemical stake.
Upon doing so, it unleashes alchemical substances and causes a
giant explosion.
Can be activated while climbing an enemy.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases damage of skill.
LV.6: Increases number of hits and the surrounding
enemies are affected by the explosion.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
  <message>
    <key>CUSTOM_SKILL_INFO_09_113</key>
    <original>垂直に跳び上がり、空中に錬成物質で生成した罠を
配置する。その後、後方に素早く身を引く
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP毎に罠の攻撃回数上昇
LV.６で空中でも発動可能&lt;/COL&gt;</original>
    <translation>Jump up and form a trap from an
alchemical substance in the air. When deployed,
quickly launch backwards.
&lt;COL ffdc78&gt;LV UP: Increases number of trap activations.
LV.6: Allows activation while mid-air.&lt;/COL&gt;</translation>
  </message>
</resource>
